<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="result_meaning">
        <item>Your measurement indicates a very high tension index and an excellent recovery ability. Although you are very tense, your ability to recover is great. This means that you have sufficient resources to cope with current and future challenges and to recover from them quickly.</item>
        <item>Your measurement indicates a very high tension index and a good recovery ability. Despite the very high tension, you still have enough reserves to cope with challenges and also to recover from them.</item>
        <item>Your measurement indicates a very high tension index and a satisfactory recovery ability. Despite the very high tension, you still have some reserves left to cope with challenges and also to recover from them. As soon as you can, try to take some time out to relax in order to restore your reserves fully and get ready for the next challenge.</item>
        <item>Your measurement indicates a very high tension index and a poor recovery ability. This means that your resources are depleted and your body is overwhelmed with the current challenges. It is important for your health that you take some time out to recharge your batteries.</item>
        <item>Your measurement indicates a high tension index and an excellent recovery ability. Although you are tense, your ability to recover is great. This means that you have sufficient resources to cope with current and future challenges and recover from them quickly.</item>
        <item>Your measurement indicates a high tension index and a good recovery ability. Although you are tense, you have sufficient resources to successfully recover from current and future challenges.</item>
        <item>Your measurement indicates a high tension index and a satisfactory recovery ability. Despite the high tension, you still have some reserves left to cope with challenges and also to recover from them. As soon as you can, try to take some time out to relax in order to restore your reserves fully and get ready for the next challenge.</item>
        <item>Your measurement indicates a high tension index and a poor recovery ability. This means that your resources are exhausted and your body is overwhelmed with the current challenges. It is important for your health that you take some time out to recharge your batteries.</item>
        <item>Your measurement indicates a medium tension index and an excellent recovery ability. This healthy tension and great recovery ability show that you have sufficient resources to cope with current and future challenges and to recover from them quickly.</item>
        <item>Your measurement indicates a medium tension index and a good recovery ability. This healthy tension and the adequate recovery ability show that you have sufficient resources to cope with current and future challenges and to recover from them quickly.</item>
        <item>Your measurement indicates a medium tension index and a satisfactory recovery ability. Your health is not negatively affected by the current tension. However, your body might soon run out of energy reserves to cope with increased stress. Take some time out to relax in order to restore your full reserves and get ready for the next challenge.</item>
        <item>Your measurement indicates a medium tension index and a poor recovery ability. The low recovery ability shows that your resources are exhausted and your body is overwhelmed with the current challenges. It is important for your health that you take some time out to recharge your batteries.</item>
        <item>Your measurement indicates a low tension index and an excellent recovery ability. The low tension and great recovery ability show that you have more than enough resources to cope with current and future challenges and to recover from them quickly.</item>
        <item>Your measurement indicates a low tension index and a good recovery ability. The low tension and the adequate recovery ability show that you have enough resources to cope with current and future challenges and to recover from them quickly.</item>
        <item>Your measurement indicates a low tension index and a satisfactory recovery ability. You are not tense. However, your body might soon run out of energy reserves to cope with increased stress. Take some time out to relax in order to restore your reserves fully and get ready for the next challenge.</item>
        <item>Your measurement indicates a low tension index and a poor recovery ability. Even though you are not tense, your body does not have sufficient energy reserves to cope with increased stress. Take some time out to relax in order to restore your reserves fully and get ready for the next challenge.</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="stress_index_gradient">
        <item>@color/color_value_d</item>
        <item>@color/color_value_a</item>
        <item>@color/color_value_b</item>
        <item>@color/color_value_c</item>
        <item>@color/color_value_d</item>
        <!--    sweep gradient has to have same color on start and end to look smooth    -->
    </array>
    <color name="black">#FF000000</color>
    <color name="color_on_value">#ffffff</color>
    <color name="color_value_a">#31bfde</color>
    <color name="color_value_b">#36cb83</color>
    <color name="color_value_c">#ffb629</color>
    <color name="color_value_d">#ff6c4c</color>
    <color name="history_chart_text">#9B9BA4</color>
    <color name="japanese_laurel">#03A900</color>
    <color name="measurement_on_preview">#fff</color>
    <color name="measurement_preview">#900</color>
    <color name="measurement_preview_disabled">#000</color>
    <color name="monza">#E2002D</color>
    <color name="persimmon">#FF6C4C</color>
    <color name="purple_200">#FFBB86FC</color>
    <color name="purple_500">#FF6200EE</color>
    <color name="purple_700">#FF3700B3</color>
    <color name="silver">#BDBDBD</color>
    <color name="teal_200">#FF03DAC5</color>
    <color name="teal_700">#FF018786</color>
    <color name="white">#FFFFFFFF</color>
    <color name="zest">#E56B26</color>
    <string name="Reminder_baseline_title">Baseline reminder</string>
    <string name="Reminder_tension_description">We recommend measuring your tension index daily to check your progress and get accurate results.</string>
    <string name="Reminder_tension_title">Reduce your tension</string>
    <string name="Results_subjective_rating">To provide you with more precise information of your state, please rate whether the interpretation you see reflects your current state:</string>
    <string name="Results_subjective_rating_2">It reflects to a small extent</string>
    <string name="Results_subjective_rating_3">It doesn’t reflect at all</string>
    <string name="Results_subjective_rating_4">It reflects completely</string>
    <string name="activity_argue">Argue</string>
    <string name="activity_commute">Commute</string>
    <string name="activity_do_chores">Do chores</string>
    <string name="activity_eat">Eat</string>
    <string name="activity_holiday">Holiday</string>
    <string name="activity_labour_work">Physical labor</string>
    <string name="activity_learning">Learn</string>
    <string name="activity_meditate">Meditate</string>
    <string name="activity_meditation">Meditate</string>
    <string name="activity_reading">Read</string>
    <string name="activity_rest">Rest</string>
    <string name="activity_screen_time">Have screen time</string>
    <string name="activity_sleeping">Sleep</string>
    <string name="activity_socialize">Socialize</string>
    <string name="activity_sport">Exercise</string>
    <string name="activity_study">Study</string>
    <string name="activity_walking">Walk</string>
    <string name="activity_working">Work</string>
    <string name="after_exercise">After Exercise</string>
    <string name="average">Average</string>
    <string name="avg_hr">Avg. HR</string>
    <string name="baseline_feedback">Great, now that we have the Baseline Measurement we can start the Biofeedback Exercise. On the next screen you will see some instructions about the exercise.</string>
    <string name="baseline_measurement">Baseline Measurement</string>
    <string name="beat_by_min">beat/min</string>
    <string name="before_exercise">Before Exercise</string>
    <string name="better_mood">better</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_baseline_1">Before starting the breathing exercise, we will take a quick measurement of your baseline HRV (Heart Rate Variability)</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_baseline_2">Please sit still and hold the finger on the camera, slightly beside the flash, not on the flash</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_baseline_3">Cover the back camera fully with your finger, without applying too much pressure</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_baseline_4">Sit upright comfortably without moving</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_baseline_5">Check your HRV before the Breathing Exercise</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_breath_cycle">Breath Cycle</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_countdown">Countdown</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_cycle_counter_1">Cycle</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="biofeedback_cycle_counter_2">%d of %d</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_exercise">Biofeedback Exercise</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_exhale">EXHALE</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_hold">HOLD</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_inhale">INHALE</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_instruction_1">please sit straight, in a comfortable position</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_instruction_2">breathe in when the circle gets bigger</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_instruction_3">breathe out when the circle gets smaller</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_instruction_4">make sure that your finger stays on the phone back camera</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_instruction_5">remember to breathe into your belly and not your chest</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_instruction_6">inhale through your nose and exhale through your mouth</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_introduction_1">Biofeedback is a mind-body technique enabling you to learn about your physiological responses and how to change them to improve your health, well-being, and performance. By monitoring your vital signs, you can gain control over physiological processes that are usually considered unconscious or automatic.</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_introduction_10">Breathing out through pursed lips will reduce the effort that exhalation takes and gives you more control over your breathing pace.</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_introduction_2">With our biofeedback exercise, we will help you to enhance the connection between your heart and brain. HRV-Biofeedback has been shown to have beneficial effects on several health issues ranging from chronic pain to anxiety and depression.</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_introduction_3">To have a good understanding of how to breathe right, try the following exercise without the smartphone:</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_introduction_4">Sit in an upright position, relax your shoulders, shifting them downward away from the ears.</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_introduction_5">Put the left hand on your chest and the right hand on your stomach.</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_introduction_6">Without straining or pushing, breathe in through your nose and feel the air moving through your nostrils. Exhale slowly through pursed lips (as if you were whistling). With your right hand feel your belly getting bigger during the inhalation phase, and smaller during the exhalation phase.The left hand on the chest should not move.</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_introduction_7">The position you adopt for sitting (upright, with relaxed shoulders) will help you to relax some of your upper body muscles and better regulate your respiration performance</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_introduction_8">Placing your hands on your chest and abdomen will enhance your perception of how your body changes during abdominal breathing and will help you reproduce these changes in the long term. Abdominal breathing is the most efficient way to breathe, maximizing the expansion ability of the lungs.</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_introduction_9">Breathing in through your nose will filter, humidify and warm up the inhaled air. Some research indicates that this type of breathing activates brain centers responsible for sensory experiences.</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_no_history">You haven’t recorded any biofeedback exercise yet.</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_results_1">All progress takes place outside the comfort zone.</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_results_2">Your HR Range has improved by:</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_results_3">You now have better regulation over your emotions and increased resilience to stress.</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_start_exercise">Start Exercise</string>
    <string name="biofeedback_tagline">See how your heart is follows your breathing</string>
    <string name="breathing">Breathing</string>
    <string name="caffeine">Caffeine</string>
    <string name="caffeine_never">I never have caffeine</string>
    <string name="camera_darc1">Unfortunately, it seems like this module of your Android phone does not support our measurement</string>
    <string name="camera_darc2">We are sorry for the inconvenience. \nWe are working on it!</string>
    <string name="camera_error">It seems like something went wrong</string>
    <string name="camera_error1">Try to gently place your finger on the camera, keeping it 2-3 mm away from the flash</string>
    <string name="camera_error2">Try to use another finger to get a better result</string>
    <string name="camera_error3">Try to apply less pressure on the camera</string>
    <string name="camera_error4">Try to sit comfortably without moving</string>
    <string name="camera_introduction1">Sit still and try not to move or speak.</string>
    <string name="camera_introduction1.1">Please hold your phone vertically.</string>
    <string name="camera_introduction2">Gently place your finger on the camera, keeping it 2-3 mm away from the flash.</string>
    <string name="camera_introduction2.0">2-3 mm</string>
    <string name="camera_introduction2.2">If the signal is poor, try to move your finger closer to the flash. Also, try to increase or decrease the pressure applied on the camera to improve signal quality.</string>
    <string name="camera_introduction2.3">If your finger gets too hot, please end the measurement and start again once the camera cooled down.</string>
    <string name="camera_introduction3">Do not apply too much pressure on the camera.</string>
    <string name="camera_introduction4">When the inner circle appears completely red, the signal is strongest and you will see your pulse wave appear on the screen.</string>
    <string name="camera_introduction4.1">The signal that we measure is displayed as waves. You can distinguish a good signal from a \"noisy\" one as shown below. A real pulse contains clear peaks and valleys as repetitive elements.</string>
    <string name="camera_introduction5">After the measurement, we will ask you some questions to enable a more detailed interpretation of your results.</string>
    <string name="camera_onboarding">For your phone this is the best camera to use</string>
    <string name="dropdown_error">Please select a value from the list</string>
    <string name="error_camera_tip">Try to gently place your finger on the camera, keeping it 2-3 mm away from the flash</string>
    <string name="error_finger_tip">Try to use another finger to get a better result</string>
    <string name="error_moving_tip">Try to sit comfortably without moving</string>
    <string name="error_pressure_tip">Try to apply less pressure on the camera</string>
    <string name="error_restart">New measurement</string>
    <string name="error_title">It seems like something went wrong</string>
    <string name="experience_negative">Negative</string>
    <string name="experience_positive">Positive</string>
    <string name="feeling_angry">Angry</string>
    <string name="feeling_anxious">Anxious</string>
    <string name="feeling_depressed">Depressed</string>
    <string name="feeling_hungover">Hungover</string>
    <string name="feeling_lonely">Lonely</string>
    <string name="feeling_moody">Moody</string>
    <string name="feeling_pain">Pain</string>
    <string name="feeling_sad">Sad</string>
    <string name="feeling_stressed">Stressed</string>
    <string name="health_insight">Health insight</string>
    <string name="heart_rate">Heart Rate</string>
    <string name="higher_pulse">higher</string>
    <string name="hrv_metrics">HRV Metrics</string>
    <string name="instruction_best_camera">best camera for measurement</string>
    <string name="introduction">Introduction</string>
    <string name="last_month">Last month</string>
    <string name="last_week">Last week</string>
    <string name="last_year">Last year</string>
    <string name="less_able_to_recover">less able to recover</string>
    <string name="less_stressed">less tense</string>
    <string name="low_battery1">Your battery is too low to perform a measurement</string>
    <string name="low_battery2">The flash of your phone is currently unavailable due to low battery. Unfortunately, without the flash we cannot accurately measure your pulse. Please charge your phone and try again later.</string>
    <string name="lower_pulse">lower</string>
    <string name="measurement_backtoback_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="measurement_backtoback_hide_more">...hide more</string>
    <string name="measurement_backtoback_popup_body">You are repeating your measurement too soon. Your results might differ from previous tests.</string>
    <string name="measurement_backtoback_popup_body2_point1">Heart rate variability (HRV) is a highly sensitive marker of your body’s stress response and is affected by several factors: the activity performed before the measurement, the time of day, your body position or breathing pace, and more.</string>
    <string name="measurement_backtoback_popup_body2_point2">HRV readings repeated in a short time range are more likely to reflect small changes in measurement conditions rather than the body’s well-being.</string>
    <string name="measurement_backtoback_popup_body2_point3">We suggest tracking HRV at selected, meaningful moments throughout the day, week, and/or month; for example, before, during and after work, physical exercise or relaxation activities.</string>
    <string name="measurement_backtoback_popup_title">Caution</string>
    <string name="measurement_backtoback_see_more">...see more</string>
    <string name="measurement_caffeinenicotine">Did you have any of this less than one hour before the measurement:</string>
    <string name="measurement_caffeinenicotine_result1">Caffeine</string>
    <string name="measurement_caffeinenicotine_result2">Nicotine</string>
    <string name="measurement_caffeinenicotine_result3">Alcohol</string>
    <string name="measurement_congratulation">Well done!</string>
    <string name="measurement_finger_lost_camera">Put your finger on the camera</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_apr">Apr</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_aug">Aug</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_day">Day</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_dec">Dec</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_feb">Feb</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_fri">Fri</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_hours">hours</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_insight">Insight</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_jan">Jan</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_jul">Jul</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_jun">Jun</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_last">Last measurement:</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_mar">Mar</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_may">May</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_mon">Mon</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_month">Month</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_mood">This overview shows how your mood has changed over time.</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_more">More ></string>
    <string name="measurement_history_nov">Nov</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_oct">Oct</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_pulse">This overview shows how your pulse has changed over time.</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_recovery">This index reflects the energy reserves you had at the time of a measurement. The higher the value, the faster you were able to recover from stress.</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_result_recovery">Recovery</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_result_tension">Tension</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_sat">Sat</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_sep">Sep</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_sun">Sun</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_tension">This result is a measure of the tension in your cardiovascular system. Low values indicate a state of relaxation, whereas high values indicate a state of stress.</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_thu">Thu</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_title">My History</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_tue">Tue</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_wed">Wed</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_week">Week</string>
    <string name="measurement_history_year">Year</string>
    <string name="measurement_onboarding_finger_camera">Gently place your finger on the camera, keeping it 2–3 mm away from the flash</string>
    <string name="measurement_onboarding_finger_sensor">Put your finger on the heart rate sensor</string>
    <string name="measurement_onboarding_next">Got it</string>
    <string name="measurement_onboarding_pressure">Don\'t apply too much pressure</string>
    <string name="measurement_onboarding_questions">Please answer the questions that follow in order to get a detail-based result</string>
    <string name="measurement_onboarding_sitting">Sit comfortably and do not move</string>
    <string name="measurement_onboarding_start">Start</string>
    <string name="measurement_onboarding_wave">When the inner circle appears completely colored, the signal is strongest and you’ll see your pulse wave appear on the screen</string>
    <string name="measurement_pulse_label">bpm</string>
    <string name="measurement_quality">Signal quality</string>
    <string name="measurement_quality_bad">Try to stay still &amp; steady</string>
    <string name="measurement_quality_good">Well done, keep going!</string>
    <string name="measurement_screen_finger_reminder">In order to get better results, please keep your finger as still as possible during the measurement.</string>
    <string name="min_hr_max_hr">Min. HR - Max. HR</string>
    <string name="mood_bad">Bad</string>
    <string name="mood_good">Good</string>
    <string name="mood_happy">Excellent</string>
    <string name="mood_neutral">Neutral</string>
    <string name="mood_okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="mood_somewhat_bad">Somewhat bad</string>
    <string name="mood_somewhat_good">Somewhat good</string>
    <string name="mood_very_bad">Very bad</string>
    <string name="mood_very_good">Very good</string>
    <string name="more_able_to_recover">more able to recover</string>
    <string name="more_result">More</string>
    <string name="more_stressed">more tense</string>
    <string name="multiple_answers_allowed">multiple answers allowed</string>
    <string name="nicotine">Nicotine</string>
    <string name="nicotine_never">I never have nicotine</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="no_measurement_last_month">No measurement last month</string>
    <string name="no_measurement_last_week">No measurement last week</string>
    <string name="no_measurement_last_year">No measurement last year</string>
    <string name="no_measurement_this_month">No measurement this month</string>
    <string name="no_measurement_this_week">No measurement this week</string>
    <string name="no_measurement_this_year">No measurement this year</string>
    <string name="no_measurement_today">No measurement today</string>
    <string name="no_measurement_yesterday">No measurement yesterday</string>
    <string name="none_of_the_above">None of the above</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata">And that is to improve:</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_condition">Are you satisfied with your physical condition?</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_condition1">Definitely not</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_condition1.2">It could be better</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_condition1.3">It is okay</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_condition1.4">Yes, I am in a good condition</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_condition1.5">My condition is excellent</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_disorder">Have you ever been diagnosed with any of the diseases or health disorders listed here?</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_disorder0">none</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_disorder1">accident injuries</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_disorder10">congenital diseases/disorders</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_disorder11">oncological diseases</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_disorder12">bones and joints</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_disorder2">diseases of the musculoskeletal system</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_disorder3">cardiovascular diseases</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_disorder4">respiratory diseases</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_disorder5">psychological impairments</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_disorder6">neurological impairments</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_disorder7">diseases of the digestive system</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_disorder8">skin diseases</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_disorder9">metabolic diseases</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_education1">What is your highest level of education?</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_education1.1">High school or equivalent</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_education1.2">Technical certificate</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_education1.3">University degree</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_education1.4">Doctor</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_education2">Please describe your current job status. You are:</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_education2.1">Student</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_education2.2">University student</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_education2.3">Trainee</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_education2.4">Employee</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_education2.5">Freelance</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_education2.6">Businessman / Company owner</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_education2.7">Unemployed</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_eval">To get an individualized evaluation of your results, please answer a few questions first.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_exercise">How do you estimate your average physical activity during a week (brisk walking, jogging, cycling, swimming, playing sports or any exercise that increases breathing and heart rate continuously for at least 20 minutes)?</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_exercise2">Low - once per week or less</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_exercise2.1">Medium - 2-3 times per week</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_exercise2.2">High - 4-5 times per week or more</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_final">If you skip the questionnaire, we unfortunately cannot offer you a precise interpretation of your results. \n\nDo you still wish to skip this question?</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_history">Do you have family history of cardiovascular diseases? (i.e. father or brother who had a heart attack by age 55, or mother or sister who had a heart attack by age 65)</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_jobillness">Does an illness or injury currently hinder you at work?</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_jobillness1">I can do my work, but I have discomfort due to a health issue</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_jobillness2">Due to a health issue, I am sometimes forced to work slower</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_jobillness3">Due to a health issue, I am often forced to work slower</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_jobillness4">Due to a health issue, I am only able to work part-time</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_jobillness5">I am not able to work</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_medication">Are you currently taking medication on a regular basis?</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_medication1">cardiovascular functioning</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_medication2">metabolism</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_medication3">breathing</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_medication4">digestion</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_medication5">mental performance</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_medication6">bones and joints</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_medication7">pain relief</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances1">How many cigarettes do you usually smoke?</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances1.2">Never smoked</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances1.3">Ex smoker</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances1.4">&lt; 10 cigarettes/day</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances1.5">&lt; 20 cigarettes/day</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances1.6">> 20 cigarettes/day</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances2">How often do you consume alcoholic beverages?</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances2.1">Not at all</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances2.2">1-2 times a week</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances2.3">3-4 times a week</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances2.4">5-6 times a week</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances2.5">Daily</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances3">What is the usual amount of alcohol you consume per drinking situation?</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances3.1">Less than 0.5L beer or 0.2L wine</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances3.2">0.5L beer or 0.2L wine</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances3.3">1L beer or 0.4L wine</string>
    <string name="onboarding_personaldata_substances3.4">More than 1L beer or 0.4L wine</string>
    <string name="onboarding_skip">Skip for now</string>
    <string name="onboarding_thankyou">Thank you!</string>
    <string name="onboarding_thankyou2">Your answers now allow us to evaluate your results with higher precision.\nReady for your first personalized measurement?</string>
    <string name="onboarding_thankyou3">Back to main page</string>
    <string name="onboarding_thankyou4">Go to measurement</string>
    <string name="optional">optional</string>
    <string name="personaldata_age">When were you born?</string>
    <string name="personaldata_age1">Enter your birth year</string>
    <string name="personaldata_error_title">Please try again!</string>
    <string name="personaldata_gender">Please select your gender</string>
    <string name="personaldata_gender1">Female</string>
    <string name="personaldata_gender2">Male</string>
    <string name="personaldata_gender3">Diverse</string>
    <string name="personaldata_height">What is your height?</string>
    <string name="personaldata_height1">Enter your height</string>
    <string name="personaldata_height_cm">cm</string>
    <string name="personaldata_height_ft">ft</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="personaldata_range_error">The value that you have entered seems unlikely. Please enter a value between %s - %s.</string>
    <string name="personaldata_weight">What is your weight?</string>
    <string name="personaldata_weight1">Enter your weight</string>
    <string name="personaldata_weight_kg">kg</string>
    <string name="personaldata_weight_lbs">lb</string>
    <string name="physically_great">Fantastic</string>
    <string name="physically_pain">Tense</string>
    <string name="physically_sick">Sick</string>
    <string name="physically_tired">Tired</string>
    <string name="pulse_high">High</string>
    <string name="pulse_low">Low</string>
    <string name="pulse_medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="pulse_normal">Normal</string>
    <string name="pulse_very_high">Very High</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_activity_title">What did you do right before the measurement?</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_caffeine">Did you have any caffeine 1 hour before the measurement?</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_exercise_title">Have you taken part in any intensive physical activity in the past 24 hours? </string>
    <string name="questionnaire_experience_title">Was your activity before the measurement a positive or negative experience?</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_feeling_title">Do you currently feel...?</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_food_title">Have you eaten in the past two hours?</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_leave_message">Tap back button again to abort the measurement</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_mood_header">How are you feeling right now?</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_next">Next</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_nicotine">Did you have any nicotine 1 hour before the measurement?</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_note_header">Would you like to write a note for today?</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_physically">How do you feel physically?</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_physically_details">Could you give a detailed description?</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_physically_hint">Today I feel…</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_physically_hint1">Today I did...</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_physically_hint2">My aim for today is...</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_show_results">See results</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_sleep_title">How did you sleep last night?</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_substances_title">Did you consume any of the following substances before the measurement?</string>
    <string name="recover_title">Recovery Ability</string>
    <string name="recovery_desc_excellent">You are able to recover very well.</string>
    <string name="recovery_desc_good">You are able to recover well.</string>
    <string name="recovery_desc_okay">You are able to partially recover.</string>
    <string name="recovery_desc_poor">You have difficulties to recover.</string>
    <string name="recovery_status_excellent">Excellent</string>
    <string name="recovery_status_good">Good</string>
    <string name="recovery_status_okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="recovery_status_poor">Poor</string>
    <string name="reminder_baseline_description">The baseline measurement should be done before you get up from bed (before standing up) and before any drink/cigarette consumption.</string>
    <string name="reminder_general">set</string>
    <string name="reminder_general_afternoon">afternoon</string>
    <string name="reminder_general_evening">evening</string>
    <string name="reminder_general_morning">morning</string>
    <string name="result_details_title">Measurement details</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_affect">What affects the result and how can it be improved?</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_affect_mood_bad">Currently, you are in a bad mood. Your mood can have a big impact on your emotional but also on your physical state. Try to become more aware of the effect your mood has on your body to have more control over your responses to daily challenges.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_affect_mood_good">Currently, you are in a good mood. Your mood can have a big impact on your emotional but also on your physical state. Try to become more aware of the effect your mood has on your body to have more control over your responses to daily challenges.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_affect_mood_happy">Currently, you are in an excellent mood. Your mood can have a big impact on your emotional but also on your physical state. Try to become more aware of the effect your mood has on your body to have more control over your responses to daily challenges.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_affect_mood_okay">Currently, you are feeling okay. Your mood can have a big impact on your emotional but also on your physical state. Try to become more aware of the effect your mood has on your body to have more control over your responses to daily challenges.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_affect_pulse">\n        • Activity: When you exercise, your pulse naturally rises. While resting, sitting or standing, your heart rate usually does not change. However, it may increase slightly during the first 15 seconds of standing and then settle back down.\n\n        • Emotions: If you feel stressed, anxious, or euphoric, your pulse may increase. Whereas, if you feel tired, the pulse decreases.\n\n        • Medications: Medications that inhibit your adrenaline, called beta blockers, usually slow down your pulse, whereas, some thyroid medications may increase it.\n\n        • Body size: Obesity can cause an increase in the resting pulse (usually no more than 100 beats per minute).\n\n        •Temperature: When the air temperature and humidity are high, your heart pumps more blood, which can cause a slight increase in pulse rate (between 5 and 10 beats per minute).\n    </string>
    <string name="result_dialog_affect_recovery_excellent">You currently have excellent energy reserves and are well prepared to recover from present and future challenges. You can easily relax and recharge your batteries.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_affect_recovery_good">You currently have enough energy reserves and are well prepared to recover from present and future challenges. Nevertheless, make sure that you do not overstrain your body and occasionally allow yourself some time off.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_affect_recovery_okay">Your body is slowly running out of energy reserves. Therefore, it will be difficult for you to recover from present and future stress and strains. Take some time and allow yourself a break to rebuild your reserves.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_affect_recovery_poor">At the moment, you have hardly any energy reserves left. Therefore, it will be extremely difficult for you to recover from present and future challenges. It is crucial that you take time to recharge your batteries.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_affect_stress_high">You have a high tension index, which is a hallmark of cardiovascular system stress. We are all exposed to a variety of stress factors on a daily basis. But our individual response to stress can be crucial for our health. Try to observe how you are feeling and acknowledge what is stressing you. Take a minute to reflect and process this information, so that you can pay better attention to your body and your needs in the future.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_affect_stress_low">You have a low tension index. This indicates that your cardiovascular system works efficiently, with few resources being invested in current activities. However, this may still lead to an overly relaxed state that makes you feel lethargic. Our bodies need a certain amount of tension in order to be alert and function at their best. Try to stand up and move a little, take deep breaths or simply do a few quick stretches to activate your body.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_affect_stress_medium">You have a medium tension index, which indicates that your body is in a balanced state. It is alert and full of energy. This state is optimal because a slight healthy tension helps us to be attentive and agile and makes the body function at its best.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_affect_stress_very_high">You have a very high tension index, which is a hallmark of high cardiovascular system stress. Possible causes are physical strain, pressure to perform, interpersonal problems or other stressful situations, unhealthy habits, or pharmacological treatment. It is crucial that you take time to consider the factors that are affecting your current state. This will help you to prevent stress in the future and improve the quality of your life in the long run.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_meaning">What does this mean?</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_meaning_pulse_high">Your pulse is relatively high. If you have taken medication, exercised or felt very stressed right before the measurement, these may be the reasons for your elevated pulse. Otherwise, a high pulse indicates that at the moment, your cardiovascular system is not working efficiently. Sometimes, it can reflect a prolonged or chronic stress state. You may want to discuss the causes of your elevated heart rate with your doctor.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_meaning_pulse_low">Your heart rate is relatively low. As long as you have not taken any medication before the measurement and are not tired, this indicates that your cardiovascular system is working very efficiently. Relatively few heartbeats are needed to supply blood to your organs.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_meaning_pulse_normal">Your heart rate looks normal. It takes an average number of heartbeats to supply your organs with blood.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_meaning_recovery">This index reflects your available energy reserves. Your body needs these reserves to recover from challenges and to quickly adjust to subtle changes in the environment. The higher the value, the faster you will be able to recover from stress.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_meaning_stress">This result is a measure of the tension in your cardiovascular system. The lower the value, the more relaxed you are. The higher the value, the more tense you are.</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_title_mood">Your mood</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_title_pulse">Your pulse</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_title_recovery">Your recovery ability</string>
    <string name="result_dialog_title_stress">Your Tension Index</string>
    <string name="result_explanation">What does this mean?</string>
    <string name="result_finish_button">Finish</string>
    <string name="result_header">Your measurement result</string>
    <string name="result_mood_title">Mood</string>
    <string name="result_pulse_title">Pulse</string>
    <string name="result_stress_index">Tension Index</string>
    <string name="show_more_measurements">Show more measurements</string>
    <string name="sleep_average">Averagely</string>
    <string name="sleep_badly">Badly</string>
    <string name="sleep_somewhat_badly">Somewhat badly</string>
    <string name="sleep_somewhat_well">Somewhat well</string>
    <string name="sleep_very_badly">Very badly</string>
    <string name="sleep_very_well">Very well</string>
    <string name="sleep_well">Well</string>
    <string name="start_baseline">Start Baseline</string>
    <string name="stress_desc_high">You are quite tense.</string>
    <string name="stress_desc_low">You are not tense.</string>
    <string name="stress_desc_medium">You are slightly tense.</string>
    <string name="stress_desc_very_high">You are very tense.</string>
    <string name="stress_high_recovery_high">Your measurement indicates a high tension index and a good recovery ability. Although you are tense, you have sufficient resources to successfully recover from current and future challenges.</string>
    <string name="stress_high_recovery_low">Your measurement indicates a high tension index and a poor recovery ability. This means that your resources are exhausted and your body is overwhelmed with the current challenges. It is important for your health that you take some time out to recharge your batteries.</string>
    <string name="stress_high_recovery_medium">Your measurement indicates a high tension index and a satisfactory recovery ability. Despite the high tension, you still have some reserves left to cope with challenges and also to recover from them. As soon as you can, try to take some time out to relax in order to restore your reserves fully and get ready for the next challenge.</string>
    <string name="stress_high_recovery_very_high">Your measurement indicates a high tension index and an excellent recovery ability. Although you are tense, your ability to recover is great. This means that you have sufficient resources to cope with current and future challenges and recover from them quickly.</string>
    <string name="stress_level_high">High</string>
    <string name="stress_level_low">Low</string>
    <string name="stress_level_medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="stress_level_very_high">Very High</string>
    <string name="stress_low_recovery_high">Your measurement indicates a low tension index and a good recovery ability. The low tension and the adequate recovery ability show that you have enough resources to cope with current and future challenges and to recover from them quickly.</string>
    <string name="stress_low_recovery_low">Your measurement indicates a low tension index and a poor recovery ability. Even though you are not tense, your body does not have sufficient energy reserves to cope with increased stress. Take some time out to relax in order to restore your reserves fully and get ready for the next challenge.</string>
    <string name="stress_low_recovery_medium">Your measurement indicates a low tension index and a satisfactory recovery ability. You are not tense. However, your body might soon run out of energy reserves to cope with increased stress. Take some time out to relax in order to restore your reserves fully and get ready for the next challenge.</string>
    <string name="stress_low_recovery_very_high">Your measurement indicates a low tension index and an excellent recovery ability. The low tension and great recovery ability show that you have more than enough resources to cope with current and future challenges and to recover from them quickly.</string>
    <string name="stress_medium_recovery_high">Your measurement indicates a medium tension index and a good recovery ability. This healthy tension and the adequate recovery ability show that you have sufficient resources to cope with current and future challenges and to recover from them quickly.</string>
    <string name="stress_medium_recovery_low">Your measurement indicates a medium tension index and a poor recovery ability. The low recovery ability shows that your resources are exhausted and your body is overwhelmed with the current challenges. It is important for your health that you take some time out to recharge your batteries.</string>
    <string name="stress_medium_recovery_medium">Your measurement indicates a medium tension index and a satisfactory recovery ability. Your health is not negatively affected by the current tension. However, your body might soon run out of energy reserves to cope with increased stress.Take some time out to relax in order to restore your full reserves and get ready for the next challenge.</string>
    <string name="stress_medium_recovery_very_high">Your measurement indicates a medium tension index and an excellent recovery ability. This healthy tension and great recovery ability show that you have sufficient resources to cope with current and future challenges and to recover from them quickly.</string>
    <string name="stress_very_high_recovery_high">Your measurement indicates a very high tension index and a good recovery ability. Despite the very high tension, you still have enough reserves to cope with challenges and also to recover from them.</string>
    <string name="stress_very_high_recovery_low">Your measurement indicates a very high tension index and a poor recovery ability. This means that your resources are depleted and your body is overwhelmed with the current challenges. It is important for your health that you take some time out to recharge your batteries.</string>
    <string name="stress_very_high_recovery_medium">Your measurement indicates a very high tension index and a satisfactory recovery ability. Despite the very high tension, you still have some reserves left to cope with challenges and also to recover from them. As soon as you can, try to take some time out to relax in order to restore your reserves fully and get ready for the next challenge.</string>
    <string name="stress_very_high_recovery_very_high">Your measurement indicates a very high tension index and an excellent recovery ability. Although you are very tense, your ability to recover is great. This means that you have sufficient resources to cope with current and future challenges and to recover from them quickly.</string>
    <string name="substances_24h_before">&lt; 24h before measurement</string>
    <string name="substances_2h_before">&lt; 2h before measurement</string>
    <string name="substances_caffeine_theine">Caffeine or Theine</string>
    <string name="substances_cardioactive">e.g. cardioactive medications</string>
    <string name="substances_other">Other</string>
    <string name="the_same">the same</string>
    <string name="this_month">This month</string>
    <string name="this_month_as_last_month">this month as last month</string>
    <string name="this_month_than_last_month">this month than the previous month</string>
    <string name="this_week">This week</string>
    <string name="this_week_as_last_week">this week as last week</string>
    <string name="this_week_than_last_week">this week than the previous week</string>
    <string name="this_year">This year</string>
    <string name="this_year_as_last_year">this year as last year</string>
    <string name="this_year_than_last_year">this year than the previous year</string>
    <string name="title_mood">Mood</string>
    <string name="title_pulse">Pulse</string>
    <string name="title_recovery_ability">Recovery ability</string>
    <string name="title_stress_index">Tension index</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="today_as_yesterday">today as yesterday</string>
    <string name="today_beginning">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="today_beginning1">Time for your first HRV measurement!</string>
    <string name="today_beginning2">Start checking your tension index, recovery ability and pulse</string>
    <string name="today_beginning3">Establish your HRV baseline</string>
    <string name="today_beginning4">0/4 days completed</string>
    <string name="today_beginning5">Complete your baseline measurements to get personalized and more accurate results</string>
    <string name="today_history">Your HRV measurement history</string>
    <string name="today_history2">Check how your tension level developed over time.</string>
    <string name="today_history3">History</string>
    <string name="today_learnmore">Learn more</string>
    <string name="today_questionnaire">To get individualized interpretation of your results, please answer our questionnaires according to our suggested frequency.</string>
    <string name="today_start">Start measurement</string>
    <string name="today_then_yesterday">today than yesterday</string>
    <string name="try_again">Try Again</string>
    <string name="worse_mood">worse</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="yesterday">Yesterday</string>
    <string name="you_are">You\'re</string>
    <string name="your_baseline_results">Your Baseline Results</string>
    <string name="your_mood_is">Your mood is</string>
    <string name="your_pulse_is">Your pulse is</string>
    <string name="your_recovery_ability_is">Your recovery ability is</string>
    <string name="your_results">Your Results</string>
    <string name="your_stress_index_is">Your tension index is</string>
</resources>